Preliminary Guide to the John Tate Lanning papers, 1926-1976
Duke University. University Archives
- Container List:
  - United States Government (Box 18)
  - University Bylaws Committee, 1960-1961, [3 folders] (Box 18)
  - University Council Meetings (Box 18)
  - University Council Summaries (Box 18)
  - University in the Kingdom of Guatemala (Box 18)
  - University Long-Range Planning (Box 18)
  - University Microfilms (Box 18)
  - University of North Carolina Press (Box 18)
  - University Research Council, [3 folders] (Box 18)
  - University Travel, Bureau of (Box 18)
  - V (Box 18)
  - V, Correspondence while Hispanic American Historical Review Editor (Box 18)
  - Valencia, Luis Avaria (Box 18)
  - Valle, Rafael Heliodore (Box 18)
  - Van Aken, Mark J. (Box 18)
  - Varela, Aurea (Box 18)
  - Vargas Ubarte, Ruben (Box 18)
  - Vila, Perez (Box 18)
  - W, [2 folders] (Box 18)
  - W, Correspondence while Hispanic American Historical Review Editor (Box 18)
  - Wagner, H.R. (Box 18)
  - Wahlquist, John T. (Box 18)
  - Walker, Maria Lia de (Box 18)
  - Walser, Dick (Box 18)
  - Wannamake, W.H. (Box 18)
  - Warner, Ralph E. (Box 18)
  - Warren, Harris G. (Box 18)
  - Watston, Richard L. (Box 18)
  - Watters, Mary (Box 18)
  - Wharton, G.W. (Box 18)
  - Wheeler, Roderick (Box 18)
  - White, Newman Ivey (Box 18)
  - Whitaker, Arthur P., [2 folders] (Box 19)
  - Who's Who in America (Box 19)
  - Wilgus, A. Curtis (Box 19)
  - Williams, Mary Wilhelmine (Box 19)
  - Wilson, H.W. Company (Box 19)
  - Wilson, Robert R. (Box 19)
  - Wilson, William J. (Box 19)
  - Wise, Jennings (Box 19)
  - Woodham, John E. (Box 19)
  - Woodlinger (Box 19)
  - Worchester, Donald E. (Box 19)
  - Wright, Almon (Box 19)
  - Wright, Irene (Box 19)
  - Y (Box 19)
  - Yanez, Agustin (Box 19)
  - Z (Box 19)
  - Zavala, Silvio (Box 19)
  - Lecture Notes (Box 20)
  - Drafts of Publications (Box 21)
  - Research Notes (Box 22)
  - Papers on the University of Mexico (Box 22)
  - Notes and Exams while a Student at University of California (Box 22)
  - Lecture Notes (Box 23)
  - Pedro de la Torre, Manuscript (Box 23)
  - Interviews on John Tate Lanning for Dict. Of N.C. Biography (Box 24)
  - Rough Drafts of Publications (Box 24)
  - Transcriptions of Documents (Box 24)
  - Research Notes (Box 24)
  - Lecture notes and course descriptions (Box 25)
  - Lecture notes (Box 26)
  - Receipts from trip to Mexico (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 26)
Related Material
Department of History records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Hispanic American Historical Review records.
University Archives, Duke University.